[
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "Which of these is a boolean value",
    "options": ["yes", "no .", "true", "int"],
    "answer": "true",
    "explanation": "boolean values are true or false"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": " what will 5 % 2 return ",
    "options": ["3", "2.5", "2", "1"],
    "answer": "1",
    "explanation": "modulus denoted by % stands for division remainder"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "what is the keyword used for a variable that should never change",
    "options": ["const", "let", "var", "fixed"],
    "answer": "const",
    "explanation": "const variable for variables that remain constant through out the operation"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "what is the javascript main function in a webpage",
    "options": [
      "making a webpage interactive",
      "creating the layout for a webpage",
      "styling webpages",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "making a webpage interactive",
    "explanation": "javascript is used for making webpages interactive"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "What does the acronym CSS stand for?",
    "options": [
      "a number",
      "a picture in your code",
      "a container or box for storing data",
      "cascading style sheet"
    ],
    "answer": "cascading style sheet",
    "explanation": "cascading style sheet."
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "which of the following is the correct way of declaring a variable",
    "options": [
      "const age = 13",
      "var = age 13",
      "let = age 13",
      "variable age = 13"
    ],
    "answer": "const age = 13",
    "explanation": "the keyword comes first, followed by variable name, equals sign and the value"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "what data type is used for text",
    "options": ["number", "string", "boolean", "integer"],
    "answer": "string",
    "explanation": "strings are for texts"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "The joining of strings together is known as _____________________",
    "options": ["string sum", "joining", "concatenation", "addition"],
    "answer": "concatenation",
    "explanation": "concatenation is the addition of strings"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "which operator is used for multiplication",
    "options": ["x", "%", "*", "/"],
    "answer": "*",
    "explanation": "the asterisk symbol is used for multiplication"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "What command is used to display messages in javascript",
    "options": ["alert()", "console.log()", "show()", "run()"],
    "answer": "console.log()",
    "explanation": "console.log is used to print in javascript"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "which operator is used for multiplication",
    "options": ["x", "%", "*", "/"],
    "answer": "*",
    "explanation": "the asterisk symbol is used for multiplication"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 1,
    "question": "What command is used to display messages in javascript",
    "options": ["alert()", "console.log()", "show()", "run()"],
    "answer": "console.log()",
    "explanation": "console.log is used to print in javascript"
  },

  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "Which of these is a boolean value",
    "options": ["yes", "no .", "true", "int"],
    "answer": "true",
    "explanation": "boolean values are true or false"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": " what will 5 % 2 return ",
    "options": ["3", "2.5", "2", "1"],
    "answer": "1",
    "explanation": "modulus denoted by % stands for division remainder"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "what is the keyword used for a variable that should never change",
    "options": ["const", "let", "var", "fixed"],
    "answer": "const",
    "explanation": "const variable for variables that remain constant through out the operation"
  },

  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "what is the javascript main function in a webpage",
    "options": [
      "making a webpage interactive",
      "creating the layout for a webpage",
      "styling webpages",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "making a webpage interactive",
    "explanation": "javascript is used for making webpages interactive"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "What does the acronym CSS stand for?",
    "options": [
      "a number",
      "a picture in your code",
      "a container or box for storing data",
      "cascading style sheet"
    ],
    "answer": "cascading style sheet",
    "explanation": "cascading style sheet."
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "which of the following is the correct way of declaring a variable",
    "options": [
      "const age = 13",
      "var = age 13",
      "let = age 13",
      "variable age = 13"
    ],
    "answer": "const age = 13",
    "explanation": "the keyword comes first, followed by variable name, equals sign and the value"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "what data type is used for text",
    "options": ["number", "string", "boolean", "integer"],
    "answer": "string",
    "explanation": "strings are for texts"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "The joining of strings together is known as _____________________",
    "options": ["string sum", "joining", "concatenation", "addition"],
    "answer": "concatenation",
    "explanation": "concatenation is the addition of strings"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "which operator is used for multiplication",
    "options": ["x", "%", "*", "/"],
    "answer": "*",
    "explanation": "the asterisk symbol is used for multiplication"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "What command is used to display messages in javascript",
    "options": ["alert()", "console.log()", "show()", "run()"],
    "answer": "console.log()",
    "explanation": "console.log is used to print in javascript"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "which operator is used for multiplication",
    "options": ["x", "%", "*", "/"],
    "answer": "*",
    "explanation": "the asterisk symbol is used for multiplication"
  },
  {
    "paperId": 2,
    "question": "What command is used to display messages in javascript",
    "options": ["alert()", "console.log()", "show()", "run()"],
    "answer": "console.log()",
    "explanation": "console.log is used to print in javascript"
  }
]